<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>LGBR</title>
 <link href="http://logansorese.com.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://logansorese.com.com/"/>
 <updated>2016-12-27T17:07:34-08:00</updated>
 <id>http://logansorese.com.com</id>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Well, okay.</title>
   <link href="http://logansorese.com.com/2016/12/27/many/"/>
   <updated>2016-12-27T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
   <id>http://logansorese.com.com/2016/12/27/many</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-letter-to-js-about-bikes&quot;&gt;A letter to J.S about bikes.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m interested in buying a bicycle for city commuting and occasional longer rides on flat, desert roads. Any advice on any of the following questions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixie bikes are dumb, right? And mountain bikes look like the cargo shorts of the bike world, right? What are the other options?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Is buying a used bike a reasonable idea or is there value in buying new?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Similar to 2: what’s the maximum I should intend to spend before it becomes extortion?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do flame decals make it faster?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;doctors&quot;&gt;Doctors&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My grandfather died of pancreatic cancer because he didn’t go to a doctor when he started getting symptoms. He let it go until he couldn’t sit down anymore because of the pain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m going to a doctor tomorrow for peace of mind. I feel okay, I can run 4 miles without much consideration, and I haven’t passed out recently. Overall, I think I’m healthy. Whether or not I am is up to the doctor’s interpretation, but I feel pretty confident.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wasn’t healthy in my younger years. &lt;em&gt;A.&lt;/em&gt; likes to goof that I didn’t learn about drinking water until my twenties. My parents bought me boxes upon boxes of Mountain Dew for most of my childhood – some kind of misplaced belief that I’d be happier if I got the noxious green liquids I wanted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took me a while to realize that I’m going to die one day. In my younger days, I treated nihilism as a means to an end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If I have nihilism, I don’t need to decide how to spend my life.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If I have nihilism, I don’t need to do anything productive.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If I have nihilism, I’ll never die because I was never truly alive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I am alive. I’m active and I’m concerned about what story I’m going to make. I care now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;las-vegas&quot;&gt;Las Vegas&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Las Vegas was created by the mob. Later, the government ate the mob whole and they assimilated into the entire system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;hemingways-second-poem-to-mary&quot;&gt;Hemingway’s Second Poem to Mary.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In the next war we shall bury the dead in cellaphane&lt;br /&gt;
     The host shall come packaged in every K ration.&lt;br /&gt;
Every man shall be provided with a small but perfect&lt;br /&gt;
     Archbishop Spellman, which shall be self-inflatable.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>A Letter to B.B.</title>
   <link href="http://logansorese.com.com/2016/11/27/ben/"/>
   <updated>2016-11-27T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
   <id>http://logansorese.com.com/2016/11/27/ben</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hey B.B.,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working on a weekend? Did M. ask you to tackle that weird missing video issue? I didn’t feel like working today. Long weekend, feeling sluggish after family and eating lots of food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel like I don’t understand what’s happening at your office anymore. I’m working remote across timezones, there’s distance between coasts and working hours. We’re all probably at fault.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not really good at communicating if you’re not directly in front of my face; I’ve learned that over that past few months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we were at the original office at the bottom of the hill, I lined random junk on the ledge by my desk with fond memories from Pittsburgh. A box of salt and corn nuts from a punk band playing in a basement in Oakland. A small rock, stolen from my boss’ desk from my first shitty job after college. A random card from Danielle’s kid. A pegacorn from… drawing a blank. No clue where that one came from.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we moved into that office at the top of the hill and I really wanted my own space. I’d never had one and it sounded so nice to get away from everyone; a little quiet I told myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I built myself a nest. A dark, lightless nest of an office with no desk-space and decreasing number of knicknacks. First they didn’t fit on my desk, then in my drawers, and then I started passing them out to everyone in the office to get them out of my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had so much space in my nest, but no space for any personality. I tried to limit myself to the point where I moved my desk onto my macbook and then I moved away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you still like your knickknacks,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Logan.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Weirdest. Music. Ever</title>
   <link href="http://logansorese.com.com/2016/11/14/weirdest-band-ever/"/>
   <updated>2016-11-14T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
   <id>http://logansorese.com.com/2016/11/14/weirdest-band-ever</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
	&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/FL-ixFZwzQU&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like when music makes uncomfortable. Weird chords, songs about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gXaUZO6gvu8&quot;&gt;bad, bad things&lt;/a&gt;, I’m on an endless search for music to hurt my head just a little.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Above is 385, a Japanese jazzcore&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Jazz&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Jazz&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; which formed in the rubble of Bleach03, an all female punk rock band from the early 2000s. They were recently featured on the show Mr. Robot&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Which&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Which&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; and have seem amount of a resurgence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this same search, I’ve come across Midori.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
	&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/566qKsQvM0g&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is more straight up experimental jazz. This song sounds like a panic attack and it’s best summed up by a lonely english comment;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;My Satan, what is this.﻿&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is grindcore, my son. It’s terrible and beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because of time restraints, I can’t fully follow this internet river much longer, but here’s a few connections for future use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c7apuNjIRe0&quot;&gt;八十八ヶ所巡礼「仏滅トリシュナー」&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3G4Znyk5b6w&quot;&gt;嘘つきバービー「嘘つきバービー学」&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Jazz&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;What a terrible name for a genre. Thrashcore? &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Jazz&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Which&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I can’t be bothered to pirate the episode right now to figure out what happened in that scene. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Which&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Document, Don't Create</title>
   <link href="http://logansorese.com.com/2016/11/01/document/"/>
   <updated>2016-11-01T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://logansorese.com.com/2016/11/01/document</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;nano&quot;&gt;Nano&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The month of November has began and that means only one thing&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Few&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Few&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;; slacking off on NanoWriMo. There’s a subreddit for people who are trying, in earnest, to get this thing done, but most already sound pretty upset about their abilities on day one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve done pretty well at sticking to things for arbitrary amounts of time. I became a runner and lost 70lbs. I’ve switched to a dumbphone for a few months to get reacquainted with that it means to be &lt;em&gt;connected&lt;/em&gt;. I’ve deleted social media and kept off of reddit for weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I can never seem to write for an extended amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I always wanted to be a writer. It’s even in my Myers-Briggs&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Myers&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Myers&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; personality test that I probably want to be a writer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s a fair amount of vanity in that quest. It’s really, really cool to be a writer. Being a writer makes a lot flaws fade away. It makes you seem smart and learned. It’d make myself feel more equipped for human life if I knew how to write about it. It’d make me feel like I know how this world works. I could build universes with my brain, put them onto paper and &lt;em&gt;I am a G*d among men, watch me create!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know what I’ll create, but I know I need to document first. I need to document what comes to my mind and not feel so precious about my ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not always feeling creative, but I can always do something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-letter-to-ce&quot;&gt;A Letter to C.E.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s quite possible that where I’m sitting now in Downtown Las Vegas is the furthest west I’ve ever been. The sun may or may not be the greatest ever here, but it’s sure as hell not the humid nightmare that is Virginia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Las Vegas has a lot to love. It’s open 24-hours so I can get Chinese food at 4am. Nearly anything you could want to do (and many you shouldn’t want to do) are legal here, so sometimes the atmosphere feels more like Bonnaroo than a city which is very freeing. Rent, food, and experiences are cheap.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The biggest negative is that you have to kind of check your ethics at the door. The financial crisis of ‘07 hit really hard over here and the unemployment rate is approaching double the national rate. There’s a HUGE homeless population that the city is, literally, trying to &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Beneath_the_Neon&quot;&gt;sweep into the sewer system&lt;/a&gt;. And the sex trade is huge and blatant and horrifying up close.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s up and coming for sure and the weirdness of legal vice takes a bit to get used to, but it’s not a bad place to spend a few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, everyone getting married is super easy to get used to, but I’m still not used to my friends having babies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;a-letter-to-the-reader&quot;&gt;A Letter to the Reader.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A day ago, I deleted my posts off of Github&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Which&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Which&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. Something about embarrassment or being unimpressed by the work I had done thus far. I believe that that was a mistake and I am sorry for my quick and shitty judgement. Now, back to our regularly scheduled programming.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was afraid that if someone read these posts in their current state, they’d think I was an idiot. With that said, I know how I scan the internet. If something isn’t interesting in 20 seconds, I dip and go somewhere else and forget about it immediately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If someone comes across this blog and is interested in what I’m saying, write me an email. You can probably find it easy enough. Write me a letter and tell me what you’re interested in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Few&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;It means a few things, really, but who’s counting? &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Few&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Myers&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.16personalities.com/infp-personality&quot;&gt;INFP Personality (The Mediator)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Myers&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Which&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This fact is already techno-funny because it’s not like Github is great at losing information. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Which&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Tech</title>
   <link href="http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/30/tech/"/>
   <updated>2016-10-30T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/30/tech</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My grandmother just sent me a text about something she saw on CNN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Hey L., I’m watching something on CNN from Silicon Valley about a young men that are hacking and women that are hacking and it looks like stuff you’d be interested in love you grandma&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She lives in Florida with her husband; both retired with a puppy they treat like a baby. When you come to town, they will give you 5🌟 accomodations for the opportunity to spend time with them. They have a laptop they use to try to communicate with her family, but they tend to call you 9 times out of 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their notion of technology is pretty clean. People learn to use computers, make things and get to paid to make things, just like everyone else has for centuries. It works like it always has.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But that concept isn’t entirely clear to me. I wouldn’t call myself a Luddite&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Ted&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Ted&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, but some of what he says makes a lot of sense. Technology destroys the environment, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bay-area-gentrification_us_56cdec76e4b041136f191b93&quot;&gt;gentrify entire states&lt;/a&gt; and makes multi-billion dollar companies who disrupt existing companies without turning any profit for decades.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are questions as to how we intend to make the morals of AI correlate to human morals. What if we dedicate billions of dollars towards sorting out “The Control Problem”&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Control&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Control&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, but we never sort out the answer? In a random universe, we can’t be sure of the answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve worked at a few technology companies and they mostly involved selling services. In-home tech support, Web Developer, Front-End Developer. They pay the bills and I can can perform the services well. I’ve always made a point to stay as far away from sales meetings as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not interested in selling anything to anyone unless I have a clear understanding of how much that thing is worth. $10,000? $300? I’m so incredibly unclear on how much any of this is worth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Ted&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;“&lt;a href=&quot;google.com/?q=lpotl&quot;&gt;I will have my revenge!&lt;/a&gt;” &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Ted&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Control&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Superintelligence:_Paths,_Dangers,_Strategies&quot;&gt;Superintelligence: Paths, Dangers, Strategies&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Control&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Famadihana</title>
   <link href="http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/29/famadihana/"/>
   <updated>2016-10-29T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/29/famadihana</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I don’t have a well-functioning relationship with the concept of death. I have been to two funerals, both for relatives, but neither for family members who I miss on a daily basis. They were good people and missed by many, but I didn’t know them well enough to appreciate their loss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, here I am, 25 years old, and completely unacquainted with the concept of losing a loved one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
	&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/UmWPkSDwtVI&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every seven years, people in Madagascar remove their family members from graves, get drunk, and dance with the corpses. Mourning are discouraged; partying is expected.  It’s a way for children in the community to learn about their ancestors and for stories to be passed down from one generation to another.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This ritual is macabre, but I’d be hard-pressed if I needed to argue that it’s a ceremony that should stop. We don’t have anything like this in the United States or any &lt;em&gt;First World Country&lt;/em&gt;; we mourn the celebrities, but we may forget our own family members. Or maybe that’s just me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t have a good sense of familial bond. Growing up, my family didn’t live near us, so we’d travel once a year at best. I still don’t feel close with them apart from the random Facebook post. I barely know where my family came from or who they were.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But there, on a tiny island country off the coast of Southeast Africa, the children are shaped by this ritual. They build a working knowledge of their ancestors and carry them on their shoulders. They tell stories together and learn about their triumphs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They’re proud of their history and part of it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Pure Garbage</title>
   <link href="http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/28/pure-garbage/"/>
   <updated>2016-10-28T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/28/pure-garbage</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It’s nice to walk and listen to a podcast. I can’t do anything other than walk and listen. On some walks, my sight is secondary and all I can do is walk and listen. This isn’t poetry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not feeling very creative this morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I moved to Pittsburgh, I worked as an in-home tech-support consultant. This service was mostly marketed to elders and luxury nursing-home residents and I would drive to them from all corners of Pittsburgh. I set my hours once a week and they’d call me during those hours with an address. I’d get a short description of the issue and drive out to their home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of them were shut-ins who had children or assistants to take care of their needs. Some of them had items stacked from floor to ceiling. Generally, they were all pleasant people and kind to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I learned how to talk to people in public and spend time with people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything I’ve just written is pure garbage.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>ngReact</title>
   <link href="http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/25/what-the-future-holds/"/>
   <updated>2016-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/25/what-the-future-holds</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;when-i-was-out&quot;&gt;When I was out.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I was out in the town, I had a beer with strangers and talked. We talked about spreadsheets and code camps. We looked at the new phones, but only saw the good in these modern marvels. We talked about community engagement and cloud storage with kind tones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We talked about mobile phones without ever checking the time. No Entry, Junior or Senior Developers. Just people, trying to be positive towards others and not fuck up too bad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kindness makes technology better. There’s a lot of evil, but 99% of what gets committed trends towards positivity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;trust-issues&quot;&gt;Trust issues.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I often believe that technology can’t be trusted. Computer intellegence, AI and Quantum technologies are becoming smarter than the beings that created them. What will make it kind? Who will design the empathy into these computers. How will we connect humans and technology without causing the destruction of one?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The answers are fundamentally unknowable, but what’s the harm for hoping? I have to ride the exponential wave of emerging technologies anyway; there’s no reason to give up now.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Late Homework</title>
   <link href="http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/25/late/"/>
   <updated>2016-10-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/25/late</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Already a couple of days into this challenge and I’ve missed a post. Didn’t even make it 5 days. I’m a failure aren’t I? I shouldn’t have bought this $10 domain name. What a waste of internet resources. Who do I think I am?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is one of those moments where I’ve need to remind myself that time is irrelevent and no one wants to hear me talking about my homework. It’s not interesting for &lt;em&gt;the audience&lt;/em&gt; and it’s sure as hell not interesting for me to re-read later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the one and only time I will write about missing a journal entry. It’s not worth the mention and it’s not worth the worry.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>In a Rush</title>
   <link href="http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/23/rush/"/>
   <updated>2016-10-23T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/23/rush</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I feel stagnant in my life because I’m rushing through it. When I tell myself to work faster, I start to believe I’m lazy because I’m not up to speed. I’m not worth the time and money spent if I can’t get my work done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;i-hate-feeling-rushed&quot;&gt;I hate feeling rushed.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I’m writing this, I am rushing to write a post before I drive to pick up my partner from work. Because I’m rushing, I don’t have anything to write about other than being rushed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With work, I’m feel rushed to be a worthwhile investment. One month into Freelancing and I’ve never felt less productive in my life. Needing to bill for hours has made me aware of how fractured my focus has become over the years. My hours mean something to my client and I need to show for their time spent. What have I spent my day doing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With my life, I feel rushed with everything. If I don’t have something to show for my 25 years, what am I worth? What am I doing if I’m not progressing towards &lt;em&gt;something&lt;/em&gt;. It’s been a while since I’ve felt like I’m &lt;em&gt;something&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Am I a programmer?&lt;/em&gt; Most of the time I think of myself as a script kiddie.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Am I a writer?&lt;/em&gt; I’m more of a journaler.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Am I a runner?&lt;/em&gt; My mile splits are chaos, let me tell you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Am I good at labeling myself?&lt;/em&gt; I’m decent, I guess.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not stagnant and I’m not lazy. I’m just trying to rush through life to get to the place where I’m happy. Yet, I might already be there, I’m just not even paying attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Excuse me as I commit this post mid-thought, quickly throw on my shoes, and hit the road.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>All Sorts of Dishonesty.</title>
   <link href="http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/22/lies/"/>
   <updated>2016-10-22T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/22/lies</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today I was feeling uneasy and unrested so I decided to take a day off. My partner went to spend time with friends who’re in town for the weekend so I read a book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I met my partner, she’s been upset at me for a number of reasons, most of which I deserve. I’m unable to wake up in the morning if I don’t have any plans&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:plans&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:plans&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. I get angry when hungry without offering her any kind of indication that I’m seconds away from becoming a living, breathing monster. I have gastrointestinal issues that can make her life unpleasant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of these, however, pale in comparison to the &lt;em&gt;big issue&lt;/em&gt;. Bigger than any fight or miscommunication we’ve ever had. &lt;strong&gt;I’ve never read The Harry Potter series.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Growing up, my brother read each book, the night it was released, with fervor. This turned me off from ever reading the series because we were very competitive as children&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:children&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:children&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. If he read a book, I’d choose another. If he learned to draw, I learned to sing&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:boyfriends&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:boyfriends&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, for the first 5 years of knowing my partner, I had zero working knowledge of the series apart from the names of the three kids, the evil baddy’s fucked up face, and &lt;span class=&quot;redacted&quot;&gt;SNAPE&lt;/span&gt; kills &lt;span class=&quot;redacted&quot;&gt;DUMBLEDORE&lt;/span&gt;. This all changed, however, when I decided to catch up for the benefit of my partner. I read through the first book, watched the second movie, read the third, fourth, fifth books and stopped. I needed to break to read other things&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Books&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Books&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; so I could I come back to the series ready to end the damn thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In that break I’ve read &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Shallows-What-Internet-Doing-Brains/dp/0393339750&quot;&gt;“The Shallows” by Nicolas Carr&lt;/a&gt; and a counterpoint from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Smarter-Than-You-Think-Technology/dp/0143125826/ref=sr_1_1?s=books&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1477191989&amp;amp;sr=1-1&amp;amp;keywords=Clive+Thompson&quot;&gt;Clive Thompson&lt;/a&gt;. I’ve internet stalked the work of a guy named “&lt;a href=&quot;http://technostism.wikia.com/wiki/Technostism&quot;&gt;Yuli-Ban&lt;/a&gt;” whose writing is monumentally well thought-out and seemingly endless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, today I’ve read most of the sixth Harry Potter book without her knowledge. She was frustrated that I stopped, but now I’m back. And doesn’t know it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a strange sensation – keeping a secret from someone – especially someone you love. In my younger years, I’d date a girl and actively line up her replacement weeks in advance of breaking up with the first girlfriend&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:former&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:former&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. I’ve stolen weed from friends; I’ve broken into people’s personal information; I’ve preemptively deleted a lot of texting conversations. I’ve held a lot of secrets and I’m not proud of all of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, this kind of secret is pleasant to hold onto. If my partner learns I’ve read the sixth book, she’ll be ecstatic. If I keep the secret for another week and finish the entire series before I tell her, she’ll probably cry with excitement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s something telling me to keep the secret; to lie to my partner for just a little longer so I can be a pleasant surprise in her life. I’ll be back, I gotta keep reading&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:goodstuff&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:goodstuff&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:plans&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Ignoring, however, that she may have plans. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:plans&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:children&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Maybe still today. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:children&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:boyfriends&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;If I had girlfriends, he had boyfriends.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Sorry&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Sorry&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:boyfriends&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Books&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I tend to read non-fiction exclusively. I’m not a big-imagination guy so it takes a lot of concentration to build a scene and follow location changes. Non-fiction doesn’t tend to have those issues. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Books&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:former&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This was always logistical nightmare, but I followed this form for 3 or 4 different cycles of girlfriends. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:former&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:goodstuff&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;It really is damn good stuff. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:goodstuff&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Sorry&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This was too funny not to write. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Sorry&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Celebrity Vampires</title>
   <link href="http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/21/sia/"/>
   <updated>2016-10-21T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/21/sia</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I’m writing this evening about something very close to my heart; the issue of celebrity vampires taking hold of our entertainment industry. This story has taken control of the media lately and it’s fair to say we’re all concerned since the leak of the “&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2016/10/20/world/vamprye-tapes-leak-what-this-means-fo?ref=world&quot;&gt;Vampyre Tapes&lt;/a&gt;”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, the conversation has grown too messy; everyone has a theory on who (or what) is leaking this information and who is/isn’t a vampire. People have resorted to violence against one another all in the name of “&lt;em&gt;ensuring the safety of our children from the powers of the underworld&lt;/em&gt;”. It’s turning into modern witch trials and everyone is already way too dramatic for their own good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do not believe that vampires are out to harm us; they want to entertain us and they want to share the knowledge they’ve gained from centuries of life on this earth. If we trust them and allow them to be open about their vampiric tendencies, we will grow stronger as a society. Vampires are people too&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Too&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Too&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. They don’t deserve how we’re treating them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/public/sia.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Sia&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sia was recently confronted by journalist Jorge Ramos on his television show and demanded she take off her beautiful white wig and show her face in a mirror. She has yet to give into this demand and no one has been able to contact her since that interview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Journalists have taken to stalking anyone Sia has ever met. Her past has become an open book and the theories are growing more absurd by the minute. Was she &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/search?q=Charlotte+Caroline+Wilhelmine+Bachmann&quot;&gt;Charlotte Caroline Wilhelmine Bachmann&lt;/a&gt;&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Predom&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Predom&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;? There are theories that she was Elizabeth I of England&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Barren&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Barren&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; and might have some legitimate right to the British throne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We might never know if these theories are true and we might never know if vampires are real, at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I do know is that Sia is a human being and has the right to privacy. Please join me in giving her space and not allowing others to devalue human rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Too&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Albeit very old ones. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Too&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Predom&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Although this theory has become the predominate one&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Archive&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Archive&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, I don’t agree. We haven’t seen any proof that Sia knows how to play an instrument (as discussed in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://thedeadhub.com/2010/04/06/sia-up-front-and-blunt/&quot;&gt;2010 interview&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;before&lt;/em&gt; the Vampyre Tapes release) and she has not shown any skill at operatic singing. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Predom&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Barren&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Being a vampire, it’d stand to reason that Elizabeth I would have been unable to produce children. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Barren&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Archive&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.org/stream/tonknstlerlexi00lede/tonknstlerlexi00lede_djvu.txt&quot;&gt;Archive from the freenode IRC Channel #vampyrehunterz (archive.org)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Archive&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Try Something.</title>
   <link href="http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/20/trying-something/"/>
   <updated>2016-10-20T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://logansorese.com.com/2016/10/20/trying-something</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I first became aware of John Zorn’s music in high school. I was dating a girl and we spent most of our time alone in her room. Her parents liked &lt;em&gt;high-school-me&lt;/em&gt; and trusted me a lot more than they should have&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Nice&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Nice&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. Every now and then, we’d be asked to spend time with her family; talking wasn’t an option, so we’d watch Netflix&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Net&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Net&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One night, we watched a film with her parents called “&lt;em&gt;Funny Games&lt;/em&gt;”. It was chosen completely at random by someone in the house; a fluke with an early algorithm. The story that unfolded was &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; brutal; a wealthy family is taken hostage in their beachfront home, two psychopaths dressed in white beam with excitement as they torture, mutilate and kill the family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;video&quot;&gt;
	&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/sHGxmOx3ReM&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a song that follows the two young killers throughout the film; a piece by John Zorn’s group &lt;em&gt;Naked City&lt;/em&gt; called “Bonehead”. The song is a loud, angry tongue thrashing by the japanese vocalist, Yamatsuka Eye, and John Zorn’s Saxophone. Lyrics and melody be damned; it’s a song that stuck with me. I memorized the sounds and carried them with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Bonehead” defined my high school experience. I joined a metal band. We were dime-store &lt;em&gt;Protest the Hero&lt;/em&gt; and the worst imitation of &lt;em&gt;The Number Twelve Looks Like You&lt;/em&gt;. We watched horror movies and ⌘-R 4chan in my parent’s unfinished basement. We talked about things being Brutal. We were brutal. &lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Brutal&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Brutal&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It encompassed my thoughts after rehearsal was over and my ears rang loudly for hours. It’s all I could hear, loud and clear, when I angrily broke up with my girlfriend and drove her home in a rainstorm. It’s what played as I sat awake at 4am and questioned every choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve listened to a lot of John Zorn in the past 48 hours; there’s a lot of music here. All good; some listenable; most aren’t my thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;high-school-me&lt;/em&gt; has different understanding on John Zorn’s than  &lt;em&gt;current-me&lt;/em&gt;. John isn’t trying to be &lt;em&gt;Brutal&lt;/em&gt;. He isn’t trying to convince you of his greatness. He isn’t questioning whether he has a valid reason to be on stage. He doesn’t care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He’s always willing to try something.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not always good, not always worth exploring, but sometimes; sometimes it’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c4eO2o9u1j0&quot;&gt;incredibly special&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know what I’m doing with this site. I don’t know what I’m doing in general. I’m just trying something.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref:Thing&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn:Thing&quot; class=&quot;footnote&quot;&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
  &lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Nice&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I wasn’t great to her; she was much nicer to me than I was to her. I can’t fix the damage ten years later, but I’m truly sorry, &lt;span class=&quot;redacted&quot;&gt;REDACTED&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Nice&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Net&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;This was back when Netflix served primarily as DVD Delivery service. Felt like magic at the time, yeah? &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Net&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Brutal&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;At least we thought so. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Brutal&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li id=&quot;fn:Thing&quot;&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;One thing a day. Reasonable amount of time to write. Minimal time available to edit. Upload immediately. Walk away. &lt;a href=&quot;#fnref:Thing&quot; class=&quot;reversefootnote&quot;&gt;&amp;#8617;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
